# EGOR KAKHNENKA

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER





+375 29 849 38 04



t.me/kahegor



kax.egor@mail.ru



Minsk, Belarus









## SKILLS

- React/Redux
- Redux-Saga/Thunk
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML/CSS
- REST API/WebSocket
- Express/MongoDB
- Material UI/ANT Design
- Unit Tests/Storybook
- Git

# LANGUAGE

- English B1(in-progress)
- Russian native

# EDUCATION

### IT-INCUBATOR

frontend developer 2021-2022

## POLOTSK STATE UNIVERSITY

construction engineer 2019 - 2020

MINSK STATE ENERGY COLLEGE construction technician 2012 - 2016

## ABOUT ME

Hi, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming. I have experience in creating a SPA with React/Redux/TypeScript. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with the help of new technologies. I'm also studying Node.js, specifically framework Express because my next goal is to become Full-Stack developer. In my free time, I try to improve my English or solve problems on Codewars.

Open to your suggestions

# EXPERIENCE

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

LeaderCode, It-Company, Dec 2021- Sep 2022,

- React development using redux, React-redux, react-router-dome, redux-saga/thunk, redux-toolkit, Axios, Formik, And-design libraries.
- Using next developer technologies:React/Redux/Redux/Rest API/Axiom/Formica/Material UI/SCSS, etc
- Checking the correctness of the code with Unit Tests, applying Storybook for demonstration of individual modules of the application. Using TypeScript for the bestcode control during development.

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

part time,2022

- Nya Cards app (3month) Stack: React, Redux, TS, Thunks, Axios, Formik, Routing, etc.
- Todolist (4month) Stack: React, Redux-Toolkit, TS, Saga, Axios, Formik, Routing, Storybook, MUI.
- Social-Network (3month) Stack: React, Redux, TS, Thunks, Axios, Formik, Routing, etc.

### **CONSTRUCTION TECHNICIAN**

Belarusian nuclear power plant, 2016 - 2019

- Team management:distribution of work/work process control
- Completion of work within the allotted time.
- Maintenance of technical documentation.